(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(شاهد على www.dramacool.club دعم الإدارة)
It's itchy and prickly, right?
إنه يسبب الحكة والوخز، أليس كذلك؟
Take off your bag and sit against the wall.
انزع حقيبتك واجلس مستنداً إلى الحائط.
Sit tight. I'll fix you up in no time.
انتظر قليلاً. سأصلح لك الأمر في لمح البصر.
Oh, I'm honestly okay.
أوه، أنا بخير بصراحة.
You're not okay.
أنت لست بخير.
I thought Si-won was home. That's why I stopped by.
ظننت أن سي-وون في المنزل. لهذا السبب مررت.
Your eye…
عينك...
You have
لديك
a cursed splinter in your eye.
شظية ملعونة في عينك.
-Sorry? -A cursed splinter.
-عفواً؟ -شظية ملعونة.
You have to yank that out for that red eye to get better.
عليك أن تخلع ذلك حتى يتحسن احمرار عينيك.
Hold it tight like this.
أمسكها بإحكام هكذا.
And hold this in your mouth. Take a full mouthful.
ضع هذا في فمك. خذ لقمة كاملة.
A mouthful.
كلام كثير.
Swish it around and spit it out here.
حركه في فمك ثم ابصقه هنا.
Spit it out.
قلها بصراحة.
Give it to me.
أعطني إياه.
Okay.
تمام.
Feels a bit better now, huh?
تشعر بتحسن طفيف الآن، أليس كذلك؟
What the heck? This is better than the hospital.
ما هذا بحق الجحيم؟ هذا أفضل من المستشفى.
You're seriously comparing me to a doctor?
هل تقارنني بالطبيب بجدية؟
I'm completely different from a doctor.
أنا مختلف تماماً عن الطبيب.
How are you different?
ما الذي يميزك؟
Anyone can become a doctor if they grind hard enough.
بإمكان أي شخص أن يصبح طبيباً إذا اجتهد بما فيه الكفاية.
But people like us? You've actually gotta be gifted.
أما أشخاص مثلنا؟ فلا بد أن يكونوا موهوبين حقاً.
An innate gift.
موهبة فطرية.
You know what I mean, don't you?
أنت تفهم ما أقصده، أليس كذلك؟
Well, go see that girl who ran away from home.
حسناً، اذهب لرؤية تلك الفتاة التي هربت من المنزل.
SI-WON
لهم
Goodbye, ma'am.
مع السلامة يا سيدتي.
Tell her not to skip her meals.
أخبرها ألا تتجاهل وجباتها.
What? You fell back asleep that quickly?
ماذا؟ هل غفوتَ مجدداً بهذه السرعة؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Aren't you cold?
ألا تشعر بالبرد؟
You should sleep at home when it's this cold.
ينبغي عليك النوم في المنزل عندما يكون الجو بارداً إلى هذا الحد.
It's even snowing outside.
حتى أن الثلج يتساقط في الخارج.
It's better than smelling like incense.
إنه أفضل من أن تفوح منه رائحة البخور.
Wait, it's snowing? In March?
لحظة، هل تمطر ثلجاً؟ في شهر مارس؟
Si-won.
لهم.
Should I join the coding club too?
هل يجب عليّ الانضمام إلى نادي البرمجة أيضاً؟
Hey, Do Hye-ryung!
مرحباً، دو هي ريونغ!
-Hurry! We'll be late if we miss the bus. -We won't be late.
- أسرعوا! سنتأخر إذا فاتتنا الحافلة. - لن نتأخر.
Slow down. We won't be late.
تمهلوا. لن نتأخر.
Seriously!
بجد!
Hey!
يا!
Hey.
يا.
Whoa, hey!
مهلاً، مهلاً!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
-Let's take our time. -What's with you?
- لنأخذ وقتنا. - ما بك؟
Hey, the bus…
يا إلهي، الحافلة...
Han Gi-tae?
هان غي تاي؟
Huh?
هاه؟
You like him, don't you?
أنتِ معجبة به، أليس كذلك؟
No, I don't.
لا أنا لا.
Want me to tell him?
هل تريدني أن أخبره؟
Hey, no. Don't ever tell him.
لا، لا تخبره أبداً.
-Are you close with Gi-tae? -Yeah.
- هل أنت مقرب من جي تاي؟ - نعم.
He joined our club, remember?
لقد انضم إلى نادينا، أتذكر؟
I was right.
كنت على حق.
You like him, huh?
أنتِ معجبة به، أليس كذلك؟
Don't worry. I'll keep your secret.
لا تقلق. سأحفظ سرك.
You mean it?
هل أنت جاد في ذلك؟
For as long as you keep my secret.
طالما أنك تحافظ على سري.
-There you are. -Goodness.
-ها أنت ذا. -يا إلهي.
-Over here. -Move over.
-هنا. -ابتعد.
It's warm.
انها دافئة.
Sit here. It's a heated seat.
اجلس هنا. إنه مقعد مُدفأ.
Oh dear.
يا عزيزي.
Sorry about that.
أعتذر عن ذلك.
Thank you, girls.
شكراً لكنّ يا فتيات.
I was half-asleep, so I wasn't sure if I really smelled incense,
كنت شبه نائم، لذلك لم أكن متأكداً مما إذا كنت قد شممت رائحة البخور حقاً.
but did you go inside my house?
لكن هل دخلتَ إلى منزلي؟
You're scary good.
أنت رائع بشكل مخيف.
You didn't pick up your phone.
لم ترد على هاتفك.
It was freezing, so I figured you'd be sleeping at home.
كان الجو بارداً جداً، لذلك افترضت أنك ستنام في المنزل.
Your mom told me to come in so she could fix my eye.
أخبرتني والدتك أن أدخل حتى تتمكن من علاج عيني.
It's one thing to come over. I told you not to play along with her.
لا بأس بالمجيء. لقد قلت لك ألا تتظاهر بالموافقة معها.
Why don't you listen?
لماذا لا تستمع؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
But it actually worked this time.
لكنها نجحت هذه المرة بالفعل.
Look. It was super red, but now you can't even tell.
انظر. كان لونه أحمر فاقعاً، لكن الآن لا يمكنك حتى ملاحظة ذلك.
You're doing this just to annoy me.
أنت تفعل هذا فقط لإزعاجي.
This wouldn't have happened if you'd picked up.
ما كان ليحدث هذا لو أنك رددت على المكالمة.
Hey, are you blaming me?
مهلاً، هل تلومني؟
If I don't, just go without me. I never asked you to come with me.
إن لم أفعل، فاذهبي بدوني. لم أطلب منكِ أبدًا أن تأتي معي.
All right.
حسنًا.
From now on, I'll just ignore your mom, no matter what she says, okay?
من الآن فصاعدًا، سأتجاهل والدتك مهما قالت، حسنًا؟
Promise.
يعد.
You actually like hanging out with someone who drinks and calls it shaman stuff?
هل تستمتع حقاً بالجلوس مع شخص يشرب الخمر ويسمي ذلك طقوساً سحرية؟
My sincerest apologies.
أعتذر بشدة.
Okay?
تمام؟
OUR FACULTY AND STAFF SUPPORT THE NEW BEGINNINGS OF ALL NEW STUDENTS
يدعم أعضاء هيئة التدريس والموظفون لدينا البدايات الجديدة لجميع الطلاب الجدد.
Good morning.
صباح الخير.
Hey, Kwon Si-won.
مرحباً، كوون سي وون.
Si-won.
لهم.
Have you decided what you're doing for the app contest?
هل قررت ما ستفعله في مسابقة التطبيقات؟
I thought about it yesterday.
فكرت في الأمر بالأمس.
-Let's talk about it in the clubroom. -Sure.
- لنتحدث عن ذلك في غرفة النادي. - بالتأكيد.
Why don't you join the coding club?
لماذا لا تنضم إلى نادي البرمجة؟
You're around this genius every day.
أنت محاط بهذا العبقري كل يوم.
Oh, can I also--
أوه، هل يمكنني أيضاً...
She's not into tinkering with machines.
إنها لا تحب العبث بالآلات.
Really?
حقًا؟
Then what are you into?
إذن، ما الذي يثير اهتمامك؟
She's… into shamanism.
إنها... مهتمة بالشامانية.
Shamanism? Like fortunetelling and stuff?
الشامانية؟ مثل التنجيم وما شابه؟
Do my fortune too.
احسب لي طالعي أيضاً.
Hey, Hee-jin.
مرحباً، هي جين.
Hey. You're actually on time for once.
مرحباً. لقد وصلت في الموعد المحدد هذه المرة.
Teacher kept bitching about how I'm dead if I'm late again.
ظلّت المعلمة تشتكي من أنني سأموت إذا تأخرت مرة أخرى.
I skipped breakfast to leave hella early. Wanna hit the cafeteria?
لم أتناول الفطور لأغادر مبكراً جداً. هل تريد الذهاب إلى الكافتيريا؟
Si-won. You should come with us.
سي-وون. يجب أن تأتي معنا.
Go on ahead.
تفضل بالمضي قدماً.
Let's hurry.
هيا بنا نسرع.
Oh, I have to go to my club today.
أوه، عليّ الذهاب إلى النادي اليوم.
Should I wait?
هل عليّ الانتظار؟
Si-won.
لهم.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Just go without me.
اذهب بدوني.
Why do you keep buying so much alcohol when you're drinking alone?
لماذا تستمر في شراء كل هذه الكمية من الكحول وأنت تشرب بمفردك؟
I'm not drinking alone.
أنا لا أشرب وحدي.
It's not like you're drinking with your high school daughter.
الأمر ليس كما لو أنك تشرب مع ابنتك في المدرسة الثانوية.
You know that's not what I mean.
أنت تعلم أن هذا ليس ما أقصده.
If you're so curious, why not come over to my place?
إذا كنت فضولياً للغاية، فلماذا لا تأتي إلى منزلي؟
My goodness.
يا إلهي.
Don't try that joke on me, you quack shaman.
لا تحاول هذه المزحة معي، أيها الدجال.
A quack?
دجال؟
Does it seem like a joke to you?
هل يبدو الأمر وكأنه مزحة بالنسبة لك؟
You really think you can hide from me?
هل تعتقد حقاً أنك تستطيع الاختباء مني؟
Hello, ma'am.
مرحباً سيدتي.
-Hello. -Yeah.
-مرحباً. -أجل.
Where's my daughter?
أين ابنتي؟
Her club will finish late.
سينتهي ناديها متأخراً.
-Oh, really? -Yes.
- أوه، حقاً؟ - نعم.
Wanna come over to my place?
هل ترغب في المجيء إلى منزلي؟
No, ma'am.
لا يا سيدتي.
Why's that?
لماذا؟
I bet you're itching to come over to my place right now.
أراهن أنك تتوق للمجيء إلى منزلي الآن.
Goodbye, ma'am.
مع السلامة يا سيدتي.
Goodness me, that hurts.
يا إلهي، هذا مؤلم.
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
Oh dear.
يا عزيزي.
"Awards. Minister's Award, one team."
"الجوائز. جائزة الوزير، فريق واحد."
"Governor's Award, one team. Superintendent's Award, two teams."
"جائزة المحافظ، لفريق واحد. جائزة المشرف، لفريقين."
Even fourth place looks good on college applications.
حتى المركز الرابع يبدو جيداً في طلبات الالتحاق بالجامعات.
You'll win for us, right?
ستفوز من أجلنا، أليس كذلك؟
Once we pick a theme, coding should be easy.
بمجرد اختيارنا للموضوع، يصبح البرمجة أمراً سهلاً.
Then while we're prepping for the contest, I'll do Si-won's snack runs.
ثم بينما نستعد للمسابقة، سأقوم أنا بجلب الوجبات الخفيفة لسي وون.
I'll also help with UI design.
سأساعد أيضاً في تصميم واجهة المستخدم.
Then I will
ثم سأفعل
grant you one wish.
سأمنحك أمنية واحدة.
Like Si-won would ever need anything from you.
وكأن سي-وون سيحتاج منك أي شيء على الإطلاق.
But her friend might.
لكن صديقتها قد تفعل ذلك.
She keeps glancing at you every day.
إنها تنظر إليك باستمرار كل يوم.
-I see Do Hye-ryung has good taste. -Hey.
- أرى أن دو هي ريونغ تتمتع بذوق رفيع. - مهلاً.
Be careful.
احرص.
She's one scary girl.
إنها فتاة مخيفة للغاية.
-Why do you say that? -Her mom's a shaman.
- لماذا تقول ذلك؟ - والدتها شامانية.
And not just any shaman, but a hella famous whack job shaman.
وليس أي شامان، بل شامان مجنون مشهور للغاية.
-This bastard's lying again. -I'm serious, dipshit.
- هذا الوغد يكذب مجدداً. - أنا جاد يا غبي.
My cousin went to Baekun Middle School.
ذهب ابن عمي إلى مدرسة بايكون المتوسطة.
I heard the daughter of a crazy shaman who drove her husband to death went there.
سمعت أن ابنة شامان مجنون تسبب في وفاة زوجها ذهبت إلى هناك.
And that
وذلك
is Do Hye-ryung.
هي دو هي ريونغ.
For real?
لريال مدريد؟
-Hey, I think it's true. -Yeah.
- مهلاً، أعتقد أن هذا صحيح. - نعم.
That's why you brought up shamanism earlier, right?
لهذا السبب ذكرت الشامانية سابقاً، أليس كذلك؟
That's enough. Let's brainstorm the theme.
هذا يكفي. لنتبادل الأفكار حول الموضوع.
Shamanism.
الشامانية.
-Hey, I like shamanism. -For the love of…
- مهلاً، أنا أحب الشامانية. - يا إلهي...
You don't wanna do the contest? Should we quit?
ألا تريد المشاركة في المسابقة؟ هل ننسحب؟
I'm talking about what you said, Gi-tae.
أنا أتحدث عما قلته يا جي-تاي.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
You just said that you'd grant any wish.
لقد قلت للتو أنك ستلبي أي أمنية.
What comes to mind when it comes to shamanism? Saju.
ما الذي يتبادر إلى ذهنك عندما يتعلق الأمر بالشامانية؟ ساجو.
So an app where you enter your saju, make a wish,
تطبيقٌ تُدخل فيه اسمك، وتتمنى أمنية.
and the wish somehow gets granted--
وتتحقق الأمنية بطريقة ما.
Hey!
يا!
Don't get carried away.
لا تنجرف وراء المشاعر.
Hear me out.
اسمعوني جيداً.
I think we're onto something. Shamanism!
أعتقد أننا توصلنا إلى شيء مهم. الشامانية!
But… what exactly is saju?
لكن... ما هو بالضبط saju؟
Isn't it your birthdate?
أليس هذا تاريخ ميلادك؟
Should we ask Do Hye-ryung?
هل نسأل دو هي ريونغ؟
If you don't want to do it, back out.
إذا كنت لا ترغب في القيام بذلك، فانسحب.
Stop distracting everyone.
توقف عن تشتيت انتباه الجميع.
Hey, Si-won.
مرحباً، سي وون.
Fuck me, that bitch is scary.
يا إلهي، تلك العاهرة مرعبة.
What did I say?
ماذا قلت؟
I told you, didn't I? You were itching to come to my place.
ألم أقل لك ذلك؟ كنتَ تتوق بشدة للمجيء إلى منزلي.
Shall I leave this here?
هل أترك هذا هنا؟
Oh, that?
أوه، هذا؟
Go leave it in that room over there.
اذهب واتركه في تلك الغرفة هناك.
You've been dying to know what's in there since last time, right?
كنت تتوق لمعرفة ما بداخله منذ المرة الماضية، أليس كذلك؟
Go ahead.
تفضل.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
You think I told you to go in there just to stare at stuff?
أتظن أنني طلبت منك الدخول إلى هناك لمجرد التحديق في الأشياء؟
It's strangely soothing, isn't it?
إنه أمر مريح بشكل غريب، أليس كذلك؟
They're cute.
إنهم لطيفون.
Pick one.
اختر واحداً.
It's a gift.
إنها هدية.
That's the one
هذا هو
you were drawn to the most?
ما الذي جذبك أكثر؟
What's the name of this one?
ما اسم هذا؟
Deolmi.
Deolmi.
You grab the scruff of someone's neck, dwitdeolmi, like this,
تمسك برقبة شخص ما، هكذا،
and shake them however you want.
ورجّها كما تشاء.
Hence the name "deolmi."
ومن هنا جاء اسم "deolmi".
You can do it too.
يمكنك فعل ذلك أيضاً.
Sorry?
آسف؟
I'm saying you can grab them and shake them however you want.
أقول لك يمكنك الإمساك بهم وهزهم كما تشاء.
Here.
هنا.
Take something that belongs to the person you want to grab by deolmi.
خذ شيئًا يخص الشخص الذي تريد الاستيلاء عليه عن طريق deolmi.
Preferably their nails, toenails, or hair.
ويفضل أن تكون أظافرهم، أو أظافر أقدامهم، أو شعرهم.
Tie that thing to the doll with the silk thread.
اربط ذلك الشيء بالدمية بخيط الحرير.
Then carve out the eyes, nose, and mouth on the face,
ثم قم بنحت العينين والأنف والفم على الوجه،
write down their saju here,
اكتب اسمهم هنا،
and spray it all over until the silk thread turns red…
ورشيها في كل مكان حتى يتحول لون خيط الحرير إلى الأحمر...
-Spray what? -Blood.
- رش ماذا؟ - دماء.
Come on, you're kidding.
هيا، أنت تمزح.
I'm not joking.
أنا لا أمزح.
Warm, fresh blood that still has life in it.
دم دافئ وطازج لا يزال فيه حياة.
I told you, didn't I?
ألم أقل لك ذلك؟
You're special.
أنت مميز.
If you do exactly as I said,
إذا فعلتَ تماماً كما قلتُ،
you can shake a person around just like with this deolmi.
يمكنك هز شخص ما تمامًا كما تفعل بهذا deolmi.
Come on, I couldn't do that.
هيا، لا أستطيع فعل ذلك.
Do you want to be my daughter?
هل تريدين أن تكوني ابنتي؟
My spirit daughter.
ابنتي الروحية.
If you're home, you should let me know!
If you're home, you should let me know!
What are you doing, sneaking around like a thief?
What are you doing, sneaking around like a thief?
A thief is better than a woman who drove her husband to death.
A thief is better than a woman who drove her husband to death.
Hey, Si-won.
Hey, Si-won.
It's a misunderstanding. This is--
It's a misunderstanding. This is--
Misunderstanding? Fuck, you were inside.
Misunderstanding? Fuck, you were inside.
Always acting friendly. Gathering evidence to blackmail me?
Always acting friendly. Gathering evidence to blackmail me?
Why would I blackmail you?
Why would I blackmail you?
Shut up and don't follow me.
Shut up and don't follow me.
It's a misunderstanding.
It's a misunderstanding.
I mean it.
I mean it.
Si-won, I'm sorry.
Si-won, I'm sorry.
Have you ever heard that if you write down your saju and make a wish,
Have you ever heard that if you write down your saju and make a wish,
it'll come true?
هل سيتحقق ذلك؟
Incense makes me wanna throw up.
Incense makes me wanna throw up.
It disgusts me when those who aren't any better than I am
It disgusts me when those who aren't any better than I am
pity me as the daughter of a shaman who drove her man to death.
pity me as the daughter of a shaman who drove her man to death.
And then there's my crazy mom, always drinking and rambling nonstop…
And then there's my crazy mom, always drinking and rambling nonstop…
FEBRUARY 1, 2005 KWON SI-WON
FEBRUARY 1, 2005 KWON SI-WON
I wish she were dead.
I wish she were dead.
That is my wish.
That is my wish.
Got any wishes you want to make?
Got any wishes you want to make?
Huh?
هاه؟
Do you have any wishes you wanna make?
Do you have any wishes you wanna make?
Yeah.
نعم.
I wish you'd accept my apology.
I wish you'd accept my apology.
Not that kind of thing.
Not that kind of thing.
A wish you'd held onto for a very long time.
A wish you'd held onto for a very long time.
A wish you couldn't tell anyone
A wish you couldn't tell anyone
and kept to yourself.
and kept to yourself.
I want Gi-tae…
I want Gi-tae…
to be my boyfriend.
to be my boyfriend.
Your biggest secret is that you like Han Gi-tae?
Your biggest secret is that you like Han Gi-tae?
Then let's do it.
Then let's do it.
Let's make a wish.
Let's make a wish.
How?
How?
My wish is that…
My wish is that…
MARCH 12, 2005 DO HYE-RYUNG
١٢ مارس ٢٠٠٥، دو هي ريونغ
…well, Gi-tae and I…
…well, Gi-tae and I…
Scratch that.
Scratch that.
Please make Gi-tae fall for me.
Please make Gi-tae fall for me.
No. I told you. That's not how you do it.
No. I told you. That's not how you do it.
Do it sincerely and wholeheartedly.
Do it sincerely and wholeheartedly.
Take it seriously, like when I confessed my secret earlier.
Take it seriously, like when I confessed my secret earlier.
And from now on,
And from now on,
all that "um, well, uh, no" crap is forbidden.
all that "um, well, uh, no" crap is forbidden.
But still--
But still--
"But still" is forbidden.
"But still" is forbidden.
It's an app test. Do we have to go this far?
It's an app test. Do we have to go this far?
And I told you. It's not "fall for me." It's "fall in love with me."
And I told you. It's not "fall for me." It's "fall in love with me."
Let me show you.
Let me show you.
"Make Gi-tae fall in love with me!"
"Make Gi-tae fall in love with me!"
Hey, "love"?
Hey, "love"?
This is so hard, seriously.
This is so hard, seriously.
Love is hard.
Love is hard.
You talk like you've been in love.
You talk like you've been in love.
Make Gi-tae fall in love with me.
Make Gi-tae fall in love with me.
Please make Gi-tae fall in love with me!
Please make Gi-tae fall in love with me!
Make Gi-tae fall in love with me,
Make Gi-tae fall in love with me,
no matter what!
no matter what!
Sometimes, I…
Sometimes, I…
Actually, often, I get scared of you.
Actually, often, I get scared of you.
Why's that?
Why's that?
Because you know me way too well.
Because you know me way too well.
Is me knowing you so well a bad thing?
Is me knowing you so well a bad thing?
Do you know why people don't like my mom?
Do you know why people don't like my mom?
She keeps seeing through…
She keeps seeing through…
the things they want to hide.
the things they want to hide.
Everyone's got a lot they want to hide.
Everyone's got a lot they want to hide.
For me, that's my home.
For me, that's my home.
I promised, didn't I?
I promised, didn't I?
That I'd keep it secret.
That I'd keep it secret.
If I make you uncomfortable,
If I make you uncomfortable,
I'll keep my distance at school.
I'll keep my distance at school.
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
But this secret is no joke either.
But this secret is no joke either.
-Hey, delete that right now. -No way.
-Hey, delete that right now. -No way.
Delete it.
Delete it.
-Come on, not cool.
-Come on, not cool.
-Come on. -Hurry up and go to sleep.
هيا بنا. أسرع واذهب للنوم.
Let's go to sleep. Now.
هيا بنا ننام. الآن.
-Let's sleep. -You need to…
- هيا ننام. - أنت بحاجة إلى...
-Go to sleep. -I'm not sleeping until you delete it.
- اذهب للنوم. - لن أنام حتى تحذفه.
That app you made… Girigo, was it? I think it'll win first place.
ذلك التطبيق الذي صنعته... جيريجو، أليس كذلك؟ أعتقد أنه سيفوز بالمركز الأول.
-Really? -Yeah. It's simple but super fun.
- حقاً؟ - نعم. إنه بسيط ولكنه ممتع للغاية.
After making my wish,
بعد أن تمنيت أمنيتي،
my heart's racing, like it's gonna come true.
قلبي يخفق بشدة، وكأن الأمر سيتحقق.
And the best part was
وكان أفضل جزء هو
that we got to share our secrets.
أننا تمكنا من مشاركة أسرارنا.
That was kinda fun.
كان ذلك ممتعاً نوعاً ما.
Let's keep our secrets.
لنحافظ على أسرارنا.
Yeah. No matter what.
أجل. مهما حدث.
Every time? What kind of "every time"?
في كل مرة؟ أي نوع من "في كل مرة"؟
You get this, right?
أنت تفهم هذا، أليس كذلك؟
And what is an "article"? An article.
وما هي "المقالة"؟ إنها مقالة.
"Every time we read an article on the Internet."
"في كل مرة نقرأ فيها مقالاً على الإنترنت."
But is that a complete sentence? Not yet.
لكن هل هذه جملة كاملة؟ ليس بعد.
What comes next? Let's see.
ماذا سيحدث بعد ذلك؟ لنرى.
See a commercial on TV or…
شاهد إعلانًا تجاريًا على التلفزيون أو...
Kwon Si-won.
كوون سي وون.
Put your phone away!
ضع هاتفك جانباً!
I'm sorry, ma'am.
أنا آسف يا سيدتي.
The "be" verb. "Likely to come into contact."
الفعل "يكون". "من المحتمل أن يحدث اتصال".
What does that mean?
ماذا يعني ذلك؟
"Be likely to" means "probably will…"
"من المحتمل أن" تعني "من المرجح أن..."
-Right? -Right.
- صحيح؟ - صحيح.
Anywhere we could smoke?
هل يوجد مكان يُسمح فيه بالتدخين؟
Yeah. Can we order anything here?
نعم. هل يمكننا طلب أي شيء من هنا؟
Maybe the wish is actually working.
ربما تكون الأمنية قد تحققت بالفعل.
I made eye contact with Gi-tae twice today.
لقد تواصلت بصرياً مع جي-تاي مرتين اليوم.
See? I told you it works.
أرأيت؟ لقد أخبرتك أنها تعمل.
Just wish for it sincerely.
أتمنى ذلك بصدق.
You like him that much?
هل تحبينه لهذه الدرجة؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
My goodness!
يا إلهي!
I'm not selling alcohol to a quack shaman!
لن أبيع الكحول لساحر دجال!
Fuck.
اللعنة.
That's probably how you drove your man to his death, huh?
ربما هكذا دفعتِ رجلك إلى حتفه، أليس كذلك؟
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
I said I'm not selling! Why cause a scene?
قلتُ إنني لن أبيع! لماذا تُثير ضجة؟
What would you fucking know?
ما الذي تعرفه أنت بحق الجحيم؟
Why come here all drunk?
لماذا تأتي إلى هنا وأنت ثمل؟
-To pick a fight? -Let go! Now!
-هل تريد افتعال شجار؟ - اتركني! الآن!
Get out of my way!
ابتعد عن طريقي!
SI-WON, DON'T STRESS TOO MUCH… YOUR MOM…
سي وون، لا تتوتر كثيراً... والدتك...
I'M AT THE HIDEOUT. WHEN ARE YOU COMING?
أنا في المخبأ. متى ستأتي؟
Hey, have you had…
هل سبق لك أن...
Hey.
يا.
Dear me.
يا إلهي.
Even your friend treats me better than you do.
حتى صديقك يعاملني أفضل منك.
Have you…
هل لديك...
My goodness. Damn it.
يا إلهي. اللعنة.
I MIGHT JUST SLEEP AT HOME TONIGHT! SEE YOU TOMORROW!
قد أنام في المنزل الليلة! أراكم غداً!
What the heck?
ما هذا بحق الجحيم؟
Goodness me.
يا إلهي!
Hair.
شعر.
My daughter's hair.
شعر ابنتي.
SEORIN
سيورين
My daughter, Si-won.
ابنتي، سي وون.
My daughter, Si-won, please…
ابنتي، سي وون، من فضلكِ...
Heavenly spirit, I'm sorry.
يا روح السماء، أنا آسف.
I'm sorry. The foolish child didn't know what she was doing.
أنا آسفة. لم تكن الطفلة الحمقاء تعرف ما تفعله.
I pray to the Bulsa Jeseok.
أصلي إلى بولسا جيسوك.
Please punish me instead of my daughter.
أرجوكم عاقبوني أنا بدلاً من ابنتي.
Please punish me instead of my daughter, Si-won.
أرجو أن تعاقبني أنا بدلاً من ابنتي، سي وون.
I pray to Hwangsa Jebul and Bulsa Jeseok.
أُصلي إلى هوانغسا جيبول وبولسا جيسوك.
Please accept my sincerity and forgive my daughter, Si-won.
أرجو أن تتقبلوا صدق مشاعري، وأن تسامحوا ابنتي، سي وون.
The call could not be connected.
تعذر الاتصال.
Hye-ryung!
هي ريونغ!
Wait.
انتظر.
You have to listen to me carefully.
عليك أن تستمع إليّ جيداً.
Put this amulet on Si-won or in her bag without her knowing, no matter what.
ضع هذه التميمة على سي وون أو في حقيبتها دون علمها، مهما حدث.
That girl takes after her father,
تلك الفتاة تشبه والدها،
so I'm sure just seeing an amulet will freak her out.
لذا أنا متأكد من أن مجرد رؤية تميمة ستصيبها بالذعر.
Still, you have to put it in without her noticing.
مع ذلك، عليك أن تضعه دون أن تلاحظ.
I couldn't save my husband, but I have to save my child at least.
لم أستطع إنقاذ زوجي، لكن عليّ إنقاذ طفلي على الأقل.
Okay?
تمام؟
Why aren't you answering? Huh?
لماذا لا تجيب؟ ها؟
You should go to the hospital first.
يجب عليك الذهاب إلى المستشفى أولاً.
You saw how I fixed your eye, right?
لقد رأيت كيف قمت بإصلاح عينك، أليس كذلك؟
I'll take care of myself, so you hurry and go to Si-won, okay?
سأعتني بنفسي، لذا أسرع واذهب إلى سي وون، حسناً؟
Get out of here!
اخرج من هنا!
Go! Now!
انطلق! الآن!
Hurry! Go now!
أسرع! انطلق الآن!
Si-won.
لهم.
-Today, at your place-- -What?
-اليوم، في منزلك-- -ماذا؟
What about my place?
ماذا عن منزلي؟
The thing is…
المسألة هي...
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
What's with her?
ما بها؟
The Road Away by Kim So-wol.
الطريق المؤدي بقلم كيم سو وول.
The thought of saying I miss you Only makes me miss you more
إن مجرد التفكير في قول "أفتقدك" يزيدني شوقاً إليك.
Perhaps I should just leave And yet, once again…
ربما ينبغي عليّ الرحيل ومع ذلك، مرة أخرى…
That girl takes after her father,
تلك الفتاة تشبه والدها،
so I'm sure just seeing an amulet will freak her out.
لذا أنا متأكد من أن مجرد رؤية تميمة ستصيبها بالذعر.
Still, you have to put it in without her noticing.
مع ذلك، عليك أن تضعه دون أن تلاحظ.
I couldn't save my husband, but I have to save my child at least.
لم أستطع إنقاذ زوجي، لكن عليّ إنقاذ طفلي على الأقل.
Okay?
تمام؟
There are crows on that mountain And crows in the field
هناك غربان على ذلك الجبل، وهناك غربان في الحقل.
They caw as the sun sets Over the western hills
يُنعقون عند غروب الشمس فوق التلال الغربية
The river…
النهر…
Seriously.
بجدية.
Be right back.
سأعود.
I'll come with you.
سآتي معك.
Hey.
يا.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
This morning, your mom--
هذا الصباح، والدتك-
It was freaking crazy.
كان الأمر جنونياً للغاية.
She slapped Do Hye-ryung and tore the amulet to shreds.
صفعت دو هي ريونغ ومزقت التميمة إلى أشلاء.
That's creepy as hell. Just wow.
هذا مرعب للغاية. يا إلهي!
Doesn't something feel off?
ألا تشعر بشيء غير طبيعي؟
She avoids talking about Do Hye-ryung,
تتجنب الحديث عن دو هي ريونغ،
and she blows up whenever shamanism comes up.
وتنفجر غضباً كلما ذُكرت الشامانية.
Maybe Kwon Si-won's the one connected to the shaman.
ربما يكون كوون سي وون هو الشخص المرتبط بالشامان.
Well,
حسنًا،
right before Do Hye-ryung got slapped,
قبل لحظات من تعرض دو هي ريونغ للصفع،
she said something weird.
قالت شيئاً غريباً.
But maybe I just misheard her.
لكن ربما أكون قد أسأت فهمها.
What did she say?
ماذا قالت؟
Just spit it out.
قلها بصراحة.
Well,
حسنًا،
Do Hye-ryung was being really careful with Si-won, and…
كانت دو هاي ريونغ حريصة للغاية مع سي وون، و...
Fucking Do Hye-ryung.
اللعنة على دو هي ريونغ.
"This morning, your mom--"
"هذا الصباح، والدتك--"
You're here.
أنت هنا.
Come check it out.
تعالَ وانظر بنفسك.
Our entry for this contest.
مشاركتنا في هذه المسابقة.
-So soon? -That was quick.
- بهذه السرعة؟ - كان ذلك سريعاً.
How did you pull this off?
كيف تمكنت من فعل ذلك؟
Isn't the design a bit too dark?
أليس التصميم داكنًا بعض الشيء؟
I like it.
أحبها.
Of course you like it. You didn't do a thing.
بالطبع أعجبك الأمر. لم تفعل شيئاً.
None of you did anything. Don't you agree?
لم يفعل أحد منكم شيئاً. ألا توافقون؟
But still…
لكن مع ذلك...
All you did was run your mouth, but you came up with the design idea.
كل ما فعلته هو أنك ثرثرت، لكنك توصلت إلى فكرة التصميم.
And you talked mad smack behind my back,
وتحدثتَ عني بكلامٍ بذيءٍ من وراء ظهري،
but you brought up shamanism.
لكنك أثرت موضوع الشامانية.
Gi-tae, you haven't contributed at all,
جي تاي، لم تُساهم بأي شيء على الإطلاق.
so help me with this.
لذا ساعدني في هذا.
Hey.
يا.
Have you heard of Girigo…
هل سمعت عن جيريجو؟
What?
ماذا؟
Have you heard of an app that grants wishes?
هل سمعت من قبل عن تطبيق يحقق الأمنيات؟
What are you saying?
ماذا تقول؟
Make Gi-tae fall in love with me.
اجعل جي تاي يقع في حبي.
What's that?
ما هذا؟
Make Gi-tae fall in love with me, no matter what!
اجعل جي تاي يقع في حبي، مهما حدث!
Hey, what's up with her?
مهلاً، ما بها؟
That's gotta be embarrassing!
لا بد أن هذا محرج!
Make Gi-tae fall in love with me, no matter what!
اجعل جي تاي يقع في حبي، مهما حدث!
Hey, it's in the group chat.
مرحباً، إنه موجود في دردشة المجموعة.
Hey, what's this?
مهلاً، ما هذا؟
Damn! So freaking embarrassing.
يا إلهي! إنه أمر محرج للغاية.
Please make Gi-tae fall in love with me!
أرجوك اجعل جي تاي يقع في حبي!
Make Gi-tae fall in love with me.
اجعل جي تاي يقع في حبي.
Make Gi-tae fall in love with me, no matter what!
اجعل جي تاي يقع في حبي، مهما حدث!
Hey.
يا.
Shamanism.
الشامانية.
Accept her confession!
اقبل اعترافها!
You really are a crazy shaman's daughter.
أنتِ حقاً ابنة شامان مجنون.
How can you believe that crap? Huh?
كيف تصدق هذا الهراء؟ هاه؟
Man, you've got shit for brains.
يا رجل، عقلك سيء للغاية.
Shit, you hear me? Huh?
يا إلهي، هل تسمعني؟ ها؟
Hey, stop filming.
مهلاً، توقف عن التصوير.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
Hey.
يا.
What makes you think you can confess to me?
ما الذي يجعلك تعتقد أنه يمكنك الاعتراف لي؟
Why the glare?
لماذا هذا الوهج؟
And you want me to love who? You crazy bitch!
وتريدينني أن أحب من؟ يا لكِ من امرأة مجنونة!
Got a death wish?
هل لديك رغبة في الموت؟
Is that enough?
هل هذا يكفي؟
HAN GI-TAE
هان غي تاي
Take something that belongs to the person you want to grab by deolmi.
خذ شيئًا يخص الشخص الذي تريد الاستيلاء عليه عن طريق deolmi.
Preferably their nails, toenails, or hair.
ويفضل أن تكون أظافرهم، أو أظافر أقدامهم، أو شعرهم.
Tie that thing to the doll with the silk thread.
اربط ذلك الشيء بالدمية بخيط الحرير.
Then carve out the eyes, nose, and mouth on the face,
ثم قم بنحت العينين والأنف والفم على الوجه،
write down their saju here,
اكتب اسمهم saju هنا،
and spray it all over until the silk thread turns red…
ورشيها في كل مكان حتى يتحول لون خيط الحرير إلى الأحمر...
-Spray what? -Blood.
- رش ماذا؟ - دماء.
Warm, fresh blood that still has life in it.
دم دافئ وطازج لا يزال فيه حياة.
MARCH 12, 2005 DO HYE-RYUNG
١٢ مارس ٢٠٠٥، دو هي ريونغ
I told you. Not just anyone can do it just by copying the steps.
قلت لك. ليس بإمكان أي شخص القيام بذلك بمجرد نسخ الخطوات.
What matters more is…
الأهم هو...
An innate gift?
موهبة فطرية؟
Yes, that's also important.
نعم، هذا مهم أيضاً.
But what's more important than that
لكن ما هو أهم من ذلك؟
is one's heart.
هو قلب المرء.
According to the scriptures,
بحسب الكتب المقدسة،
simwibeopbon simjonsimsa.
simwibeopbon simjonsimsa.
In other words, the mind is the root and master
بمعنى آخر، العقل هو الأصل والسيد
of all things.
من بين كل الأشياء.
To control one arm,
للتحكم في ذراع واحدة،
you need to offer up at least a chicken.
يجب عليك تقديم دجاجة على الأقل.
To control two arms,
للتحكم في ذراعين،
you need to offer up at least a pig.
عليك أن تقدم خنزيرًا على الأقل.
Have you ever heard that…
هل سمعت من قبل...
if you write down your saju and make a wish…
إذا كتبت اسمك وتمنيتَ أمنية...
it'll come true?
هل سيتحقق ذلك؟
Yes, that's right.
نعم، هذا صحيح.
I'll make the wish just the way you told me.
سأحقق الأمنية تماماً كما أخبرتني.
My wish is…
أمنيتي هي...
for all of you to die.
لكي تموتوا جميعاً.
That's my wish.
هذه أمنيتي.
Hey, Kwon Si-won! Did you see the video?
مرحباً، كوون سي وون! هل شاهدت الفيديو؟
Delete it before anyone sees it!
احذفها قبل أن يراها أحد!
This shit happened because you asked me to help!
هذا الهراء حدث لأنك طلبت مني المساعدة!
I'll destroy the entire server if I have to,
سأدمر الخادم بأكمله إذا اضطررت لذلك.
so shut the hell up!
إذن اصمت!
DELETE FOLDER
حذف المجلد
Damn it!
عليك اللعنة!
MULTIMEDIA ROOM CLOUD SERVER
خادم سحابي لغرفة الوسائط المتعددة
No way.
مستحيل.
Wondering what this crazy bitch is up to?
أتساءل ما الذي تخطط له هذه المرأة المجنونة؟
Yes, that's right.
نعم، هذا صحيح.
I'll make the wish just the way you told me.
سأحقق الأمنية كما طلبت مني تماماً.
My wish is…
أمنيتي هي...
for all of you to die.
"لكي تموتوا جميعاً."
Fucking hell.
يا للهول!
How could you…
كيف يمكنك...
I truly wish every one of you would just drop dead.
أتمنى حقاً أن يموت كل واحد منكم فجأة.
That's my wish.
هذه أمنيتي.
How could you do this to me…
كيف تجرؤ على فعل هذا بي؟
Fuck you, Do Hye-ryung!
تباً لكِ يا دو هي ريونغ!
FEBRUARY 1, 2005 KWON SI-WON
1 فبراير 2005 كوون سي وون
SENDING WISH…
إرسال الأمنيات…
YOUR WISH HAS BEEN GRANTED
لقد تحققت أمنيتك
IF WISHES COULD KILL
لو كانت الأمنيات قادرة على القتل
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang
ترجمة الترجمة الفرعية: سونغ إن جانغ